Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic history of Tufts College, 1904 -- 1946; MS036.001; 20.8 Linear Feet; 329 Digital Object(s)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 31, 1931-09 -- 1931-11; MS036.001.050.00001 (Volume 50)
    - Assistant to the Registrar Helen Beardsley (left) and Stenographic Assistant L. Helen Erb (right), 1931-10-22; MS036.001.050.00001.03458; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 31)
      Munro Scrapbook: Box 50, Vol. 31, Pg. 88
      People; photographic print; Erb, L. Helen; Beardsley, Helen; Office of the Registrar; Alumni Association
    - G. Stanley Perkins, Herman Tyrance, Edward A. Conley, Frank J. Vieira, and James Parr, freshman liberal arts, 1931; MS036.001.050.00001.04365; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 50)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 50, p. 17, #9594
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Perkins, G. Stanley; Tyrance, Herman; Conley, Edward A.; Vieira, Frank J.; Parr, James
    - Freshmen football squad, 1931-11-09; MS036.001.050.00001.04366; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 50)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 50, p. 133, #9757
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 32, 1931-11 -- 1932-05; MS036.001.051.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
    Alpha Tau Omega house party photos, 58-60.
    - Professors Row at winter, 1932-01-10; MS036.001.051.00001.01699; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 32, pg. 65, box 51)
      Views; photographic print
    - Professor W.C. Casson and his Austin car, 1932-01-12; MS036.001.051.00001.01700; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 32, pg. 72, box 51)
      Faculty; photographic print
    - Photo of nurse and child advertising the Children's Floating Hospital, 1932-03-09; MS036.001.051.00001.01702; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 32, pg. 103, box 51)
    - Charles Ransom '31 and Ernest Sackett '32 operating marionettes, 1932-03-10; MS036.001.051.00001.01703; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 32, pg. 108, box 51)
    - Austin Barclay Fletcher, 1932; MS036.001.051.00001.01707; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      photograph of painted portrait; in Photographic history of Tufts College, volume 32, p. 143
      photographic print; Fletcher, Austin Barclay
    - Freshman soccer team, 1931-11-20; MS036.001.051.00001.04330; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 51 p. 15 #9785
      Students; Athletics; Soccer; photographic print; Black students
    - Meeting of the Kings in the Desert, scene from the play, Le Jeux de la Nativite, 1931-12-17; MS036.001.051.00001.04331; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 51 p. 44 #9832
    - The Three Kings Tell Herod of the Birth of a New King in Bethlehem, scene from the play, Le Jeux de la Nativite, 1931-12-17; MS036.001.051.00001.04332; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 51 p. 46 #9834
    - King Herod Dismisses the Three Kings, scene from the play, Le Jeux de la Nativite, 1931-12-17; MS036.001.051.00001.04333; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 51, p. 47, #9835
    - King Jasper Pays Respect to the New Born King, scene from the play, Le Jeux de la Nativite, 1931-12-17; MS036.001.051.00001.04334; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 51, p. 50, #9838
    - King Balthasa Brings a gift of Gold to the New Born King, scene from the play, Le Jeux de la Nativite, 1931-12-17; MS036.001.051.00001.04335; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 51, p. 51, #9839
    - Mary and Joseph bid the Kings Godspeed, scene from the play, Le Jeux de la Nativite, 1931-12-17; MS036.001.051.00001.04336; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 51, p. 52, #9840
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 34, 1932-10 -- 1933-03; MS036.001.052.00001 (Volume 52)
    - Joseph Walker, 1933-03-02; MS036.001.052.00001.02946; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Photographic History of Tufts College volume 34, pg. 121. "3T3, very high in scholarship, captain of tennis team, meets college expenses by exercising his musical abilities, a typical all round college man."
      Athletics; Tennis; Students; photographic print; Black students; Walker, Joseph
    - Getting ready for the freshman sing, 1932-11-17; MS036.001.052.00001.02959; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Photographic History of Tufts College: Vol. 34, Box No. 52, p. 45.
      People; Students; Traditions; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Squash player Joan Franceschini, 1933-02-16; MS036.001.052.00001.03472; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 34, Box No. 52, Pg. 108
      People; Students; Athletics; Squash; photographic print; Franceschini, Joan; Jackson College
    - Squash players Joan Franceschini and Louise Ryan, 1933-02-06; MS036.001.052.00001.03480; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 34, Box No. 52, Pg. 107; (left to right): Joan Franceschini and Louise Ryan
      People; Students; Athletics; Squash; photographic print; Franceschini, Joan; Ryan, Mary Louise; Jackson College
    - Tufts varsity soccer squad, 1932-11-17; MS036.001.052.00001.04326; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 052, p. 48, #10177
    - Tufts basketball team, 1933-02-17; MS036.001.052.00001.04327; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 052, p. 114, #10243
      Students; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students
    - Joseph Walker, class of 1933, 1933-03-02; MS036.001.052.00001.04328; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 52, p. 121, #10251. Caption on page reads: "Very High In Scholarship--Captain of Tennis Team. Meets college expenses by exercising his musical ability. A Typical All Round College Man."
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Walker, Joseph
    - Tufts varsity basketball team, 1933-03-03; MS036.001.052.00001.04329; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 52)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 52, p. 137, #10265
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 33, 1932-05 -- 1932-11; MS036.001.053.00001 (Volume 53)
    Alumni day photos, pp61-63
    - Ballou Hall decorated for Class Day activities, 1932-06-10; MS036.001.053.00001.03464; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 53)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 33, Box No. 53, Pg. 66
      Buildings; Class Day; photographic print
    - Varsity tennis team, 1932-05-27; MS036.001.053.00001.04337; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 53)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 53, p. 52, #9991
      Students; Athletics; Tennis; photographic print; Black students
    - John Trapuzzano, Charles Hanavich, Mario Pino, Charles D. Godreau, and Phillip Heifetz, September, 1932; MS036.001.053.00001.04338; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 53)
      Date is approximate. Print is in Munro Collection, Box 53, p. 89, #10025
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Trapuzzano, John; Hanavich, Charles; Pino, Mario; Godreau, Charles D.; Heifetz, Phillip
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 35, 1933-03 -- 1933-06; MS036.001.054.00001 (Volume 54)
    Alumni day, pp 120-124
    - Tufts varsity basketball squad, 1933-04-24; MS036.001.054.00001.04368; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 54)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 054, p. 50, #10330
    - Tufts varsity tennis team, 1933-06-17; MS036.001.054.00001.04369; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 54)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 054, p. 114, #10395
      Athletics; Tennis; Students; photographic print; Black students
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 36, 1933-09 -- 1933-12; MS036.001.055.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 55)
    - Jackson students posing with Jumbo, 1933-11-25; MS036.001.055.00001.03344; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 55)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 36, Box 55, Pg. 117
      People; Students; photographic print; Cole, Alice; Hotchkiss, Helen; Marshall, Jean; Franceschini, Joan; Jackson College
    - Ivar R. Hakanson, Joseph P. Smith, R. A. Winsky, John Carey, and David D. Rose, 1933; MS036.001.055.00001.04370; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 55)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 055, p. 8, #10453
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Hakanson, Ivar R.; Smith, Joseph P.; Winsky, R. A.; Carey, John; Rose, David D.
    - Irma Thompson, Mrs. Veronica D. Dengle, Gertrude T. Elliot, Esther F. Slack, Helen G. Shats, Jackson College freshman, 1933; MS036.001.055.00001.04371; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 55)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 055, p. 21, #10496
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Thompson, Irma; Dengle, Veronica D.; Elliot, Gertrude T.; Slack, Esther F.; Shats, Helen G.; Jackson College
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 37, 1933-12 -- 1934-05; MS036.001.056.00001 (Volume 56)
    - William Johnny Grinnell, 1933-02-17; MS036.001.056.00001.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 56)
      Portrait of William G. "Johnny" Grinnell in basketball uniform. Volume 37, page 52.
      People; Basketball (Men's); Sports; Grinnell, William G. 'Johnny'; Munro, Melville S.
    - Freshman relay team, 1934; MS036.001.056.00001.04372; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 56)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 056, p. 45, #10759
      Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 38, 1934-05 -- 1934-06; MS036.001.057.00001 (Volume 57)
    - Freshman track team, 1934-05-09; MS036.001.057.00001.04373; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 57)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 057, p. 32, #10884
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 39, 1934-09 -- 1934-10; MS036.001.058.00001 (Volume 58)
    - In the Cousens Gymnasium, 1934-10-04; MS036.001.058.00001.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 58)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 58, p. 83, #11098. Caption reads: Floor treated with "Seal-O-San" wax - Huntington Laboratories, mfg. Chemists"
      Gymnasiums; Buildings; Athletics; photographic print
    - William G. Johnny Grinnell, 1935; MS036.001.058.00001.00002; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 58)
      Portrait of William G. "Johnny" Grinnell in football uniform. Volume 39, page 110.
      People; Football; Sports; Grinnell, William G. 'Johnny'; Munro, Melville S.
    - Catherine Murray playing hockey, 1934-10-25; MS036.001.058.00001.04438; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 58)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 58, p. 132, #1151
      Women; People; Students; Athletics; Field Hockey; photographic print; Murray, Catherine
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 40, 1934-10 -- 1934-12; MS036.001.059.00001 (Volume 59)
    - Staff members working in the Alumni Publicity Office, 1934-11-06; MS036.001.059.00001.03453; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 59)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 40, Box No. 59, Pg. 52; (left to right): Geraldine E. Minton, L. Helen Erb, Alicia R. Breen, Joseph W. Morton, Joan Franceschini
      People; Staff; Students; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Minton, Geraldine E.; Erb, L. Helen; Breen, Alicia R.; Morton, Joseph Webster; Franceschini, Joan; Alumni Association
    - Tufts vs. New Hampshire football game, huddle, 1934-11-03; MS036.001.059.00001.04439; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 59)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 59, p. 31, #11223
      Football; Men; People; Students; Athletics; photographic print
    - Alone in the East! drawing by Bob Coyne, 1934; MS036.001.059.00001.04440; Unknown (Volume 59)
      Date is approximate. Print is in Munro Collection, Box 59, p. 130
      Drawings; Football; photographic print
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 41, 1934-12 -- 1935-02; MS036.001.060.00001 (Volume 60)
    - Music professor Leo Lewis instructing a class, 1932-12-15; MS036.001.060.00001.03335; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 60)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol 41, Box 60, Pg. 107
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Lewis, Leo R.; Department of Music
    - Staff of the Tufts Weekly printing the most recent edition, 1934 -- 1935; MS036.001.060.00001.03476; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 60)
      (left to right) David Packard, George Auer, and E.W. Hauley; Munro Scrapbook: Vol 41, Box No. 60, Pg. 20
      People; Students; Staff; Newspapers; photographic print; Packard, David; Auer, George Jay, Jr.; Hauley, E.W.; Tufts Weekly
    - Basketball head coach Arthur M. Chochran, 1935-02-14; MS036.001.060.00001.04441; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 60)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 60, p. 116, #11464
      People; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Cochran, Arthur
    - Relay team, 1935-02-14; MS036.001.060.00001.04442; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 60)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 60, p. 116, #11472
      Athletics; Track (Men's); People; photographic print
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 42, 1935-03 -- 1935-05; MS036.001.061.00001 (Volume 61)
    - View of the the tower at Goddard Chapel and the entrance to Ballou Hall, 1930; MS036.001.061.00001.03448; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 61)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 42, Box No. 61, Pg. 101
      Buildings; Chapels; photographic print
    - Betty Schloss, new captain of swimming team, a high school poster picture, 1935-04-08; MS036.001.061.00001.04246; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 61)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 061, p. 57
      Women; Students; Swimming; photographic print; Schloss, Betty
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 43, 1935-05 -- 1935-06; MS036.001.062.00001 (Volume 62)
    - The Barnum Museum from the Quadrangle, 1935-06-13; MS036.001.062.00001.03340; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 62)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 43, Box No. 62, Pg. 115
      Buildings; Museums; photographic print
    - Group of three women with 1200 points wearing their Jackson AA blazers, June 13, 1935-06-13; MS036.001.062.00001.03479; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 62)
      (left to right) Esther Odell, Patricia Smith, and Ella Munro; Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 43, Box No. 62, Pg. 103.
      People; Students; Traditions; photographic print; Odell, Esther; Smith, Patricia Hope; Munro, Ella H.; Jackson College
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 45, 1935-10 -- 1935-12; MS036.001.063.00001 (Volume 63)
    Alpha Omicron Pi, THe JWH cup [photo and newsclipping]
    - Looking eastward from the Tufts Golf Course at the Chemical Laboratory and Jackson Gymnasium, 1930; MS036.001.063.00001.03459; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 63)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 45, Box No. 63, Pg. 44
      Buildings; Laboratories; Golf; photographic print; Dept. of Chemistry; Jackson College
    - Richard N. Current, Robert Claus, Charles F. Ranson, G. Francis Dame, and Antonio de J. Cardozo, Fletcher students, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04374; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 63)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 063, p. 109, #12147
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Current, Richard N.; Claus, Robert; Ransom, Charles F.; Dame, Francis G.; Cardozo, Antonio de J.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - Fletcher School student line-up, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04641; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 107, #12143.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Christol, Jr., Carl Q.; Highley, Jr., Albert E.; Hinz, W. Frederick; Fowle, Richard J.; Clark, Harlan B.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student line-up, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04642; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 108, #12144.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Melbourne, Roy M.; Hamilton, Kingsley W.; Christie, Jean; Lester, W. Stewart; Krieg, William L.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student line-up, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04643; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 108, #12145.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Edwards, J. Dixon; Lester, Barnett B.; Chapman, Mrs. Mildred E.; Guarniem, George T.; Stone, Waldo E.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student line-up, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04644; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 108, #12146.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Thurston, Theodore H.; Horvath, Walter J.; Fishburn, John T.; Johnson, Fremont B.; Robbins, Robert R.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student line-up, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04645; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 109, #12147.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Current, Richard N.; Claus, Robert; Ransom, Charles F.; Dame, Francis G.; Cardozo, Antonio de J.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student line-up, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04646; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 109, #12148.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Hawley, Robert B.; Kirby, Hilda; Hapgood, Richard K.; Argeaux, Maynard G.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student line-up, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04647; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 109, #12149.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Hannum, C. Suzanne; Frechtling, Louis E.; Gotthelf, Ina; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student Helen Domin, 1935; MS036.001.063.00001.04648; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 063, page 110, #12150.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Domin, Helen; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 44, 1935-06; MS036.001.064.00001 (Volume 64)
    [Alumni day] Alumni banquet, news item and photo of President Cousens; Alumni day pp9-25
    - 1920 Jackson class reunion, 1935-06-15; MS036.001.064.00001.03449; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 64)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 44, Box No. 64, Pg. 16
      People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Jackson College
    - 1920 Jackson class reunion, 1935-06-15; MS036.001.064.00001.03450; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 64)
    - Fletcher School student C. Suzanne Hannum, 1935; MS036.001.064.00001.04649; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 064, page 50, #11851.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Hannum, C. Suzanne; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student F. C. Keyes, 1935; MS036.001.064.00001.04650; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 064, page 50, #11852.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Keyes, F. C.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student Louis E. Frechtling, 1935; MS036.001.064.00001.04651; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 064, page 51, #11853.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Frechtling, Louis E.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student Albert E. Highley Jr., 1935; MS036.001.064.00001.04652; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 064, page 51, #11854.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Highley, Jr., Albert E.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student W. Frederick Hinz, 1935; MS036.001.064.00001.04653; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 064, page 52, #11855.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Hinz, W. Frederick; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Fletcher School student Roland Beyer, 1935; MS036.001.064.00001.04654; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 064, page 52, #11856.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Beyer, Roland; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 46, 1935-12 -- 1936-03; MS036.001.065.00001 (Volume 65)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 47, 1936-05 -- 1936-06; MS036.001.066.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 66)
    Alpha Tau Omega, 85.
    - Literary Lions are elected to Phi Beta Kappa, 1930-10-03; MS036.001.066.00001.02958; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 118)
      (left to right) Raymond G. Ockert and Robert W. Meserve; Photographic History of Tufts College: Vol. 47, Box No. 47, Pg. 4.
      People; Students; photographic print; Ockert, Raymond G.; Meserve, Robert W.; Phi Beta Kappa
    - Dr. Ruhl J. Bartlett, head of the Department of History, 1936; MS036.001.066.00001.04377; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 66)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 066, p. 84, #12348
      People; photographic print; Bartlett, Ruhl Jacob
    - Tufts Varsity Track Team, 1936; MS036.001.066.00001.04378; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 66)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 066, p. 126, #12386
    - Professor Ruhl J. Bartlett, 1936; MS036.001.066.00001.05184; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
      In Munro Scrapbook Vol 36, MS036/001-066, p. 84
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Bartlett, Ruhl Jacob; Dept. of History
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 49, 1936-09; MS036.001.067.00001 (Volume 67)
    Alpha Tau Omega, 43-45.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 50, 1936-10 -- 1937-03; MS036.001.068.00001 (Volume 68)
    - 1936 ice storm, November, MS036.001.068.00001.01705; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      Contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 50, pg. 57, box 68.
      Snow; Ice; Storms; Trees; photographic print
    - Bunkbeds in a bedroom of the Delta Tau House, 1921; MS036.001.068.00001.01706; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 50, pg. 37, box 68)
      Views; photographic print; Delta Tau Delta
    - Football coaches, "On the Beach", 1936; MS036.001.068.00001.04375; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 68)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 068, p. 18, #12716
      Athletics; Football; photographic print; Black students
    - Jack Gordon, Gertrude Elliot, and Joseph Smith, writers of original one act plays, 1937; MS036.001.068.00001.04376; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 68)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 068, p. 127, #12784
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Gordon, Jack; Elliot, Gertrude T.; Smith, Joseph P.
    - Wilson House living room, 1936; MS036.001.068.00001.04656; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 068, page 81, #12794.
      Housing; Dormitories; Interior views; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Wilson House living room, 1936; MS036.001.068.00001.04657; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 068, page 82, #12795.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 51, 1937-03 -- 1937-05; MS036.001.069.00001 (Volume 69)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 52, 1937-05 -- 1937-06; MS036.001.070.00001 (Volume 70)
    Alumni day news releases, clippings and photos, pp113-129